Right now, I want to get those congressmen to go and
approve it about Obamacare and all the different things
that we're working on.
One step at a time.
We'll be doing it.
Really?
I mean, that's something down the road a little bit.
A lot of people don't like that.
Frankly, you know, they consider term limits to be an
election, but I think it would be a good thing.
But right now, what I want to do is get Obamacare approved
and I want people to love us approved or change.
Well really well changed when I say Obamacare, I mean I'm talking about real change and
I suspect the first thing that's going to change will be the name, but we're talking
about repealing and replacing and if we don't do that I would be very upset.
Nobody's going to get thrown out of their insurance, are they?
Because that's what a lot of people are saying.
On the left, they're saying millions of people
are gonna lose the insurance.
No, they have it all wrong.
And you're gonna hear about it during the speech,
but they have it all wrong.
We're gonna have a really great healthcare plan,
and it's gonna be much more affordable.
Including for the country.
Now, I know when you were inaugurated,
you put your hand on your Bible
that your mother had given you as a child.
I know as a mother, as parents,
we pray for our children,
we want the best for them and your parents,
they probably pray for you so much,
but maybe not, they might not have realized
that you were gonna get this far,
and I know they would be very proud of you.
That leads me to this question.
Ronald wrote us and said, I pray for you daily.
Do you take time to pray?
I do, actually, and to me, it's very important.
But that's so nice, who is that?
That's Ronald.
Wow, hello, Ronald.
We ought to bring Ronald to the White House.
He'd be happy to come.
I like Ronald.
And this is the last one.
Alan Sherman from Queen says, I'm a diehard New York Mets fan since you're a native of the Great Barrow of Queens
But move to Manhattan are you a Mets fan or a Yankees fan the fate of the world relies on this answer?
Well, I don't think it does, but actually I do like both teams and I love this time Burner family and the Will Pond family and Randy Levine and the whole group
They Randy has done a terrific job. He's involved with the Yankees.
Now you're probably going to win New York? Well, I don't know, but I do like both teams.
I really do. What about social security? People might are worried that it might run out by the
time we need it. You're going to be okay. That was Ainsley from Manhattan.